[Aoi Toudou] The hands
will never surpass the eyes.
Unless you cultivate the
eyes to discern good from bad,
you cannot hope
to improve the hands
that create works of art.
It's a phrase that's often
used among creators,
but it applies to
all kinds of fields.
Those with good
eyes will improve
far more rapidly
than those without!
(energetic music)
(grunting)
When I throw my
right horizontal punch...
he immediately
sends a left vertical jab!
Itadori wasn't moving
like this before!
He's improving...
by devouring me!
(grunting)
What a beautiful way
to knock me down!
[Yuuji Itadori] His
face is wide open!
I can hit it!
Even with Divergent Fist!
(gasps)
Somehow he stopped
my fist with his forehead
before it could
reach full speed!
That's not exactly what I
want you to devour right now.
Your Divergent Fist is
created by your cursed energy
lagging slightly behind your
superhuman physical prowess,
when normally
there'd be no lag at all.
It's a tricky move.
Your average sorcerer
wouldn't know what happened,
and they'd be left disoriented.
It has lots of force, too.
Enough for opponents
on that level, at least.
(gasps)
But it won't work
against special-grades.
What will you do, best friend?
I'll use my full strength and
imbue it with cursed energy.
Good!
If that's so, why is your
cursed energy lagging?
I know why!
It's because you're
channeling it!
Huh?
Wait, I thought we were
talking about channeling it faster.
When we channel cursed energy,
it is a technique
that most sorcerers
are conscious of doing.
My stomach's full of rage,
or, the blood is
boiling in my gut.
The theory is that cursed energy
extracted from such negative
emotions starts in the navel
and is channeled
throughout the body.
They say it flows from
the navel to the chest,
then to the shoulders,
arms, and finally the fists.
But this view of the
body as individual parts
is what delays cursed energy.
The idea of channeling
cursed energy isn't wrong,
but that's only the first step.
You can't let yourself remain
too trapped by that concept.
The better the
sorcerer, the harder it is
to read the flow of
their cursed energy.
Yours is hard to read
for a different reason.
Would you say sorcerers
think using their guts?
Do we express
anger with our heads?
Now listen to me, Itadori.
(gasps)
(eagle screeches)
(moving orchestral music)
We exist in this world
with our entire mind,
body, and soul as one whole.
It's such a given that no
one even thinks about it.
Thank you, Toudou.
I think now...
I understand.
Good.
Then no more words are needed.
I won't hold back!
I'll guide you with
my full strength!
Don't die on me, Itadori!
Rise up to greater heights!
(Opening theme music)
(singing in Japanese)
(birds whistling)
Hey, you!
Your old fart Principal told
you to kill Itadori, didn't he?
(gasps)
This girl has good intuition!
No, Panda who figured that out.
Huh? What are you saying?
You don't need to try
and hide it from me.
I'm out to kill someone, too.
To be specific,
that watered-down
version of Maki named Mai.
Huh?
Oh don't "huh" me.
Even Pepper usually has a
wittier comeback than that one.
Why isn't this making her mad?
Instead, I'm the one
getting pissed off!
Oh right, you guys
have your own version
of Pepper don't you?
Yeah, I forgot.
Maybe I should scrap him
and dump the parts somewhere!
(eerie music)
[Panda] Scary.
Huh?
(Panda grunts)
Panda, no!
It's a cursed corpse,
so it won't die.
But it won't be able
to move for a while.
Now, who was it you
were going to scrap?
Hold on, Mechamaru.
I'll teach this first-year
she's not quite as cute
as she thinks she is.
I'll show her how
Mai has suffered,
and teach her what it means
for a woman to live
as a jujutsu sorcerer.
Just kidding!
(Panda grunts)
(grunting)
What are you trying to do?
Focus on support and
staying out of sight!
Let's just try to
get along, all right?
Since you and I are so similar.
You idiot puppet!
(mysterious music)
You don't know anything!
Oh good grief, what happened
to us hunting cursed spirits?
Sword option.
(metal clanging)
Boost on.
(blasting)
(gasps)
Ultra Spin!
(blasts)
(tree creaking)
Can't you hold still?
I need to finish this quickly.
I'd rather leave him
be and go help Nobara,
but he fires at range.
We didn't have information
on him, Nishimiya, or Miwa.
You're very strong.
What grade are you?
This is my estimate
of everyone's standing.
It's a little more than
Nobara can handle.
I don't think my rating
against cursed spirits
is important right
now, but I'll tell you.
Semi-first-grade.
[Panda] Yikes!
[Mechamaru] Ultra Cannon!
[Panda] His area
of attack is huge!
(blasts)
(dramatic music)
(exhales)
Heat emission!
It's a technique with a big
buildup and a long cool-down.
[Mechamaru] This
output is pointless
unless I hit its core dead-on.
[Masamichi Yaga] Cursed corpses.
That's the generic name
for inanimate objects
that house curses and
can operate independently.
Man-made cursed
corpses always have a core,
which serves as their heart.
I, Yaga Masamichi,
am the leading expert
on puppeteering
cursed techniques,
and Panda is my
ultimate masterpiece.
He's a cursed corpse
born with emotions.
(intense music)
A cursed corpse mutation.
Panda...
is not a panda!
(thumping)
(shouts)
(grunting)
[Mechamaru] I can't
follow his movements!
(grunting)
(dramatic music)
You know what?
I would have heard rumors
if there was someone
out there like me.
So the fact that I haven't
means that you're
not a cursed corpse.
You're a sorcerer who's
remote-controlling this thing
while your real
body is elsewhere.
So why get offended at being
treated like a cursed corpse?
Don't wanna be like me?
I feel wounded!
That is so hurtful!
Judging by your high
cursed energy output,
your main body
probably isn't too far away.
It's right outside
the arena, huh?
Guess there's no point
in hunting you down, then.
You'd just be free to
act in the meantime.
So I guess I'll
just bust you up.
You won't be doing
either of those.
Heavenly Pact.
Have you heard of it?
It's not the kind of pact
one would normally
forge with oneself.
This fateful pact
was forced on me
the second I entered this world.
I was born without a right arm
and with nothing at
all below my knees,
and I have no sensation
from the waist down.
My skin is so fragile that
even moonlight burns it.
It feels like needles
are constantly stabbing
into every pore of my body.
But in exchange
I've been granted
immense cursed energy production
and the ability to
use cursed techniques
over vast distances.
I didn't ask for
any of this power.
In fact, if I could trade
my cursed techniques
to have a normal
body, I'd gladly do so.
And so, when I see a
cursed corpse like you
walking around in broad daylight
without a care in the world...
instead of me...
I cannot stand it!!
(whirring)
Ultimate Mechamaru!
Mode: Albatross!
[Panda] That's an incredible
amount of cursed energy!
And given his position...
Nobara's in his line of fire!
I have to block it!
[Mechamaru] Ultimate Cannon!
(blasting)
(fire crackling)
Is it dead?
No. The very concept of
death doesn't apply to you.
[Panda] You revealed your
technique while complaining
about your misfortune, earlier.
Quite the sorcerer thing to do.
It's still alive?
After taking a hit
from Ultimate Cannon?
(stomp)
[Panda] I'm kind
of pissed off now.
(Mechamaru's voice quavers)
What form is that?
[Masamichi Yaga] Panda...
is not a panda!
(energetic music)
(wooden blocks clacking)
Panda...
You should know you
have an older brother
and sister.
No I don't.
Yes, but they're inside of you.
It's hard to explain.
Inside of me?
Yes.
You'll get it someday.
And in the
meantime, those two...
will always be there
to lend you strength.
[Mechamaru] Sword
Option: Ultra Shield!
(metal shattering)
(grunting)
[Panda] Normally a cursed corpse
has a single core for its heart,
but there are three
cores inside me,
and by switching out
which one is the main core,
I can convert my body.
There's the Panda
core, focused on balance,
my older brother, Gorilla Core,
focused on power for
short, decisive battles.
and my bashful older sister.
His first attack got
my older sister's core,
and that last one
exhausted the Panda core!
Now the only choice
I'm left with is...
to beat him with Gorilla Mode!
(boom)
(dramatic music)
[Mechamaru] He doesn't
pack as much power as Toudou.
But that palm strike just now...
went all the way
to my internals.
Even if I block it, I'll
still incur damage.
You get it now?
This is Gorilla
Mode's special move!
(beats chest)
The unstoppable Drumming Beat!
[Mechamaru] If I take
that Drumming Beat
to my head or chest,
I won't be able to move
Mechamaru anymore.
My right arm's Sword Option
is no longer functioning.
I can't fire Ultimate
Cannon anymore, either.
[Panda] Gorilla Mode
pounds through cursed energy
like a gorilla, but
I need to hurry.
I crushed his right arm,
so he can't fire off his
ultimate attack anymore.
And with no swords
in his left or his mouth,
he only has ranged blasts left.
Even so, he won't
fire them randomly.
Mechamaru believes he's
already failed to finish me
with those blasts
twice, when the truth is,
he actually put two of
my cores close to death.
His next move is to blast my
core with point-blank precision
or try to finish
me with a slash.
However...
(energetic music)
at close range, I
have the advantage!
(energetic rock music)
(grunting)
(intense music)
A tile?
Did he pick it off
the roof just now?
(grunts)
First a distraction,
then jet acceleration!
He's experienced at this!
[Mechamaru] This
time, I won't miss!
His cursed energy
is densest at his core!
Right here!
(groans)
You did well for a mere puppet.
(grunts)
(gasps)
[Panda] Don't treat me
like other cursed corpses.
I know how to bluff
the position of my core
with cursed energy manipulation.
I've already concealed
the number of cores I have.
(grunts)
(tiles shattering)
You lost because you
underestimated puppets.
I haven't had a single
thing in common
with anyone around me
from the moment I was born.
I thought maybe you and
I could relate to each other
because of that.
But I'm not jealous of
humans, and I never have been.
You're not?
I mean, humans are creepy.
(gasps)
(soft piano music)
They'll risk their
lives and fight hard
to reach their goals,
then suddenly turn around
and be laid-back or wishy-washy.
I don't get them.
Still, I do love those
aspects that I don't have,
creepy as they are.
You have your own
hardships too, Mechamaru.
But just having more hardships
doesn't make you right.
It's not like we're
enemies in the first place.
I mean, why'd you
become a sorcerer?
Was it just the only thing
you thought you could do?
Not that it makes
any difference.
But if you want to do
something else with your life...
I'd help you.
(sighs)
Mechamaru, don't waste
your powerful moves.
The foe in front of you
may not be the only one.
Mechamaru, someone
who can't instantly state
his type of woman can never be
a full-fledged jujutsu sorcerer.
Mechamaru, instead of
chocolate I got you some of these!
I heard the double A Evoltas
are one of your favorites.
[Mechamaru] I'm
not built like that.
(gasps)
-Liars!
-(laughing)
One day...
(sloshing)
(soft piano music)
I'll be together with everyone.
[Panda] Hm? Did
you say something?
I wonder if you'll
still say you'll help me
after you see what I look like.
Huh?
(laughing)
You think someone
who looks like me
is gonna fuss over
what you look like?
I'm a panda!
Later.
Let me pay you
a visit next time.
Shut up damn puppet.
Oh, I forgot...
Huh?
[Panda] Lend me your phone.
(birds whistling)
(swords clanging)
(grunting)
[Miwa Kasumi] No way!
This woman...
is incredibly strong!
(closing theme music)
(singing in Japanese)
-(quirky music)
-[Mechamaru] Juju Stroll.
Mechamaru, I need
you to let Noritoshi know
Utahime's calling him.
Mechamaru?
Please, take this
book to Toudou, okay?
Mechamaru!
Perfect timing.
Please, could you deliver
this box to Toudou and Kamo?
What the hell?
What do I look like,
your messenger boy?
(gasps)
(curious music)
Don't try to talk
to me right now.
Takada's live-streaming
and I intend to watch it!
Ibaragi?
You mean Ibaraki.
So how is it that
you don't know that?
[Both] Uh, because they're
too much trouble, obviously.
[Miwa] To be honest, I'm
still scared of both of them.
[All] But if I admit that,
I might not be able to
ask him favors anymore.
-Mechamaru?
-Hm?
(exciting music)
We're all counting on you!
Yeah!
(gasps)
[All] Gotta run! Time
for our missions!
Wait!
Why?
(gentle guitar music)
Oh well.
It's good that they
can rely on me...
I guess.
(intense music)
(singing in Japanese)